deal24.co.uk 2011-05-01

# Price comparison at deal24.co.uk

The security of your personal information and your privacy is very important to us as operator of deal24.co.uk (in the following just called deal24.co.uk). Since your trust in us means a lot to us, we'll do all that's possible to warrant and keep this trust. Against this background deal24.co.uk tries by all means to ensure the compliance of privacy.  
In this regard we ask you to read the privacy policy to get informed about the way we'll treat your personal information if you use our online services. Changes in this policy might happen from time to time. Of course, you'll be advised in this case and also asked to have a look at these pages again.

Furthermore we want to inform you about the following points:

  * **a)** Your Privacy
  * **b)** Minor's Privacy
  * **c)** Collecting Personal Data
  * **d)** Use Of Cookies On Our Website
  * **e)** Other Data Collection
  * **f)** Use Of Information
  * **g)** Transfer Of Personal Data
  * **h)** Viewing / Changing Your Personal Data
  * **i)** Deleting Your Account
  * **j)** How To Secure Your Personal Information From Abuse, Loss Or Other Changing
  * **k)** Protection From Web Crawlers And Spam
  * **l)** Changes To These Privacy Guidelines

#### a) Your Privacy

deal24.co.uk is brought to you by the Unister GmbH ("Preisvergleich.de"). deal24.co.uk believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our customers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, deal24.co.uk makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about deal24.co.uk's collection, use and disclosure of information you choose to share with us through our website.

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of deal24.co.uk's User Agreement. By using the site you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the site, you are also consenting to deal24.co.uk's privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### b) Minor's Privacy

deal24.co.uk is not targeted towards, or intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. By using the website you represent and warrant that you are 18 years of age or older. We reserve the right to terminate your membership in the event that deal24.co.uk becomes aware you are under 18. Persons under 18 may not submit any personally identifiable information to us, and if we discover that we have inadvertently gathered such information, we will take the appropriate steps to delete it.

#### c) Collecting Personal Data

The use of certain features and services on the site requires that you register and supply personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, telephone number and other information, which is stored by deal24.co.uk. When you register as a member of the site, we may also collect additional information from you in order to provide you with those specific services and to personalize your experience on the site.

#### d) Use Of Cookies On Our Website

deal24.co.uk uses "cookies" to automatically recognize returning users. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to display your previously defined search criteria and notification preferences whenever you visit our site. The information saved is used for the functionality of the site, for example, by recording your display preferences or regulating the frequency of pop-ups. Advertising partners also use cookies over which deal24.co.uk has no control. These are used to select customer-specific advertising.

You are free to block cookies from being saved on your hard disk by configuring your browser appropriately. It is not necessary to enable cookies to be able to use our website. However, we draw your attention to the fact that blocking cookies can lead to restricted function. 

#### e) Other Data Collection

We may get data from or about you in other ways not specifically described in this statement. For example, you might contact customer support or we may get a third party complaint about you.

#### f) Use Of Information

Information you provide to us through the website is used by deal24.co.uk to operate the website, provide you with information and services you request, and to communicate with you. We may, for example, use information you provide to target ads that we think you may be interested in, or send emails to you including newsletters and alerts. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary (such as to assist you in your use of the website). You may always choose not to provide us with this information. However, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time, however, you may not opt-out of some administrative emails (such as emails about User Agreement changes) while you are a member with our website.

#### g) Transfer Of Personal Data

Your personal data will be passed on to our customers in anonymous form only. deal24.co.uk does not publish any of your personal information without your express consent or unless we are legally obliged to do so.

#### h) Viewing / Changing Your Personal Data

You can view and, if required, change the information in your Best-Price account at any time using your deal24.co.uk login and password.

#### i) Deleting Your Account

You can delete or deactivate your Best-Price account at any time. To do so, go to the "Setting" page and click on "Cancel membership". If you cancel your membership, all your data will be permanently removed from our database. It usually takes two to three working days for all your data to be removed from all data records.

#### j) How To Secure Your Personal Information From Abuse, Loss Or Other Changing

The information in your deal24.co.uk account and in your Best-Price profile is password protected so that only you have access to your personal details. Please note that you are not permitted to give your password to any other person. deal24.co.uk will never ask you for your password in e-mails which you are not expecting or which you have not requested. Always log out of your account and close the browser window when you leave the deal24.co.uk website if you are using a shared computer in a public place. This is at present the safest way of ensuring that no-one can gain access to your personal information.

#### k) Protection From Web Crawlers And Spam

deal24.co.uk guarantees that we will only use your e-mail address with your express permission for the uses described in the conditions of use. We will not sell your e-mail address to third parties and will prevent your e-mail address from being captured by web crawlers and spiders to the extent that is it within our capability to do so. If you think that your e-mail address has been captured in this way, please contact our technical support team immediately.

#### l) Changes To These Privacy Guidelines

Any changes to the privacy guidelines will be posted on the deal24.co.uk website.
